# Ruslynn Appana

16 Cottage Cove 206 Glover Avenue, Die Hoewes 073 315 1696 ruslynn@gmail.com

#### Personal statement

A highly motivated and hardworking individual, who has matriculated and is currently in second year BSc Computer Science.

Mechanically minded, with a methodical approach to working and an eagerness to learn and develop personal skills in a practical setting. Eventual career goal is to become a fully-qualified and experienced software developer.

### **Key Skills**

- · Advanced problem solving and numeracy skills
- Accomplished communication skills, both written and verbal, developed through numerous essays and presentations given during my time at university and school.
- · Ability to take the initiative and work well under pressure.
- · Flexibility, whilst maintaining enthusiasm and commitment to each task.
- Proficiency in all areas of Microsoft Office, including Access, Excel, Word and PowerPoint
- · Highly skilled with the use of computers and most technological devices.
- · Strong management and administrative skills.
- · Ability to act independently and without constant supervision.
- Knowledge in many programming languages including:
  - o C++
  - o Java
  - o SOL
  - o HTML
  - JavaScript
  - o PHP

### Education

### Pretoria Boys High School

(2009 - 2013)

#### Matric:

- Physics B
- Maths B
- Information Technology A
- English B
- Afrikaans B
- Life Orientation A
- Biology A

# University of Pretoria

### (Current)

Modules Passed

lodui	cs i assea	
0	COS 131	Introduction to programming (C)
0	COS 110	Program Design (C++)
0	COS 151	Introduction to Computer Science
0	COS 212	Data structures and algorithms
0	IMY 310	Multimedia
0	INF 214	Informatics (SQL)
0	INL 240	Information science
0	JCP 202	Community-based project
0	PHY 114	Physics
0	PHY 124	Physics
0	OBS 114	Business management
0	<b>OBS 124</b>	Business management
0	STK 110	Statistics
0	STK 120	Statistics
0	WTW 114	Calculus
0	WTW 115	Discrete structures
0	WTW 152	Mathematical modelling
0	WTW 285	Discrete structures

# **Work Experience**

# Pretoria Boys High School Tuckshop (unpaid work experience)

(2011-2012)

#### Duties included:

- Taking orders from customers
- Stock taking
- · Packing and organising the shelves
- Closing the shop after business hours

### Data capture for CND Commodities

(2017)

### University of Pretoria Student Lab Technician (Laptop Support)

(2018-Current)

#### Duties included:

- · Fixing any software related problem that students might have
- Helping with most laptop related requests made by the various Foundations that work with the University
- · Making bookings for students to acquire help with their laptop related enquiries.

# **Accomplishments**

- South African school colours for gaming (DotA)
- 1st place in the Entelect Challenge University Cup (2018)